

About me

I am an ambitious technical college student with 11 months of experience in IT field.

I am not afraid of challenges and expanding my technical knowledge, I am open to new experiences. I am interested in new technologies and the culture of other countries.

My hobby is coffee making and the American Basketball League NBA.

Contact



LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/karol-olbryś/

E-mail

karol.a.olbrys@gmail.com

Skills

- Excel
- Word
- SQL
- IAVA
- HTML
- CSS

Technical

- Active directory
- Microsoft 365
- Intune

Hobby

- New technologies
- Basketball
- Travel

Karol Olbryś

Experience

PZU Centrum Operacji S.A

09.2023 - currently

Henke Krystian Henke 11.2020 - 04.2021

IT Support Specialist

- 2nd line support
- Providing technical support for company employees
- Managing tasks in Service Desk application
- Managing accounts in Active Directory

Internship

- Support for network hardware and business computers
- Implementation of company network migration

MYTAXI POLSKA Sp. z.o.o.

06.2019 - 08.2019

Small team coordinator

- Auxiliary work
- Company promotion
- · Collecting scooters
- Team coordination in the field

Education

10.2023 - currently

Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology

Engineering studies

Field of study: Information management Ist year

09.2018 - 05.2022

Technikum nr 1 im. Marcina Kasprzaka w Warszawie

Secondary school

I wrote my high school diploma in May 2022 with a positive result. Profile: IT Technician

Education Level: Technical

Languages

- English Fluent
- Spanish Beginner
- Technical English Continuing learning

Certificates

Diploma confirming professional qualifications "IT technician"

- No. D/77000151/23